### 1

# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

### R. PONNARASAN,

S/o,: L.Ragu,

4/372 valluvar street,

Manimedu thandalam (post) Email: <u>ponnarasan764@gmail.com</u>

Chennai 600128.

Tamil Nadu, India. Mobile: +91 9962927760

### **OBJECTIVE:**

To work in highly challenging environment as a specialized Civil Engineer where my skills and loyalty will be rewarded with career advancement.

### **EXPERIENCE SUMMARY:**

Around 3 Years of experience in Highway work. & 1 year of construction work Knowledge

#### **KEY EXPERIENCE:**

Experience in Quality Control Lab activities i.e., OGL soil sampling, Borrow area soil sampling and Conducting tests on soil as per IS codes to ensure suitability for road construction. Conducting frequency tests as per MoRT&H guidelines. Preparation of Mix Design for different grades of concrete as per requirement. Preparation of JMF for GSB, DLC according to the materials available at site. Preparing Monthly Progress Report.

Experience in site engineer activities i.e. maintaining labour & ventor management, execution of building plan & monitoring quality control

# **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:**

**B.E** (Civil),**Anna University** 

Chennai, June 2017.

# **Computer Knowledge:**

Ms Office, AUTOCAD

R.Ponnarasan CV Page 1

### **EXPERIENCE DETAILS:-**

# **❖ FROM NOVEMBER 2017 TO JUNE 2019 :**

ORGANISATION : <u>Gayatri Projects Ltd.</u>

POSITION : Quality Control Engineer.,

PROJECT : Rehabilitation and up gradation of NH-4 from km.133.360

to km.171.590 (Andhra Pradesh / Tamilnadu Border to

Nalagampalli Village) to Four lane with Paved Shoulder in

The state of Andhra Pradesh under NHDP-IV on EPC Basis

CLIENT : NATIONAL HIGHWAY DEVELOPMENT PROJECT

Authority Engineer : **M/s.** Aarvee Associates Architects Engineers Consultants

Pvt., Ltd.,

### **FROM JULY 2019 TO DECEMBER 2020:**

ORGANISATION : <u>Patel Infrastructure Ltd.</u>

POSITION : Quality Control Junior Engineer.,

**PROJECT**: Four laning of Sethiyathopu to cholapuram

From km 65.960 to km 116.440 section of NH-45C

In the state of Tamilnadu Under Phase -4 on Hybrid Annuity mode

CLIENT : NATIONAL HIGHWAY DEVELOPMENT PROJECT

Authority Engineer : Theme Engineering Service Pvt.Ltd

### ❖ FROM JANUARY 2021 TO TILL DATE:

ORGANISATION : ALIGI & CO

POSITION : SITE ENGINEER

PROJECT : Commercial building (20900 sqft area)

LOCATION : Puzhal champ, Chennai

R.Ponnarasan CV Page 2

3

## **PERSONAL PROFILE:**

NAME : **R. PONNARASAN** 

FATHER'S NAME : L. Ragu,

DATE OF BIRTH : 23 - 10 - 1995

SEX : Male

NATIONALITY : Indian

RELIGION : Hindu

MARITAL STATUS : Single

PERMANENT ADDRESS : R. PONNARASAN,

S/o L.Ragu,

4/372 Valluvar street,

Manimedu, Thandalam (post)

Chennai 600128. Tamil Nadu, India.

LANGUAGES KNOWN : Tamil, English, Telugu

I am available for immediately relocation in perusal of challenging career.

I, the undersigned, certify that to the best of my knowledge and belief, these Curriculum Vitae correctly describes me, my qualification and my experience.

Thanking you,

Thanks & Regards

R.PONNARASAN

R.Ponnarasan CV Page 3